<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AlcoSensing</string>
    <string name="consent_button">Start Consent</string>
    <string name="survey_button">Take Survey</string>
    <string name="consent_button_done">Consented</string>
    <string name="clear_button">Clear</string>
    <string name="survey">Survey</string>
    <string name="menu_data_cleared">Data has been cleared</string>
    <string name="user_name">User Name:</string>
    <string name="date_consented">Date Consented:</string>
    <string name="responses">Responses so far:</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="reqs_title">Study Requirements</string>
    <string name="prize_title">Prize Draw</string>
    <string name="reg_title">About You</string>
    <string name="consent_string">Consent</string>
    <string name="survey_title">Drinks Survey</string>
    <string name="wifi_warning">AlcoSensing needs to upload some data.\nPlease connect to WiFi.</string>
    <string name="survey_warning">AlcoSensing will send a survey soon.\nLook out for notifications.</string>
    <string name="alcosensing_name">AlcoSensing</string>
    <string name="invalid_height_under">Invalid answer, your height must be more than %1$s centimetres. </string>
    <string name="invalid_height_over">Invalid answer, your height must be less than %1$s centimetres.</string>
    <string name="invalid_weight_under">Invalid answer, your weight must be more than %1$s kilograms.</string>
    <string name="invalid_weight_over">Invalid answer, your weight must be less than %1$s kilograms.</string>
    <string name="status_screen_advice">
        <![CDATA[
           <div style=\"font-size: 0.85em\">
           Complete at least 10 survey responses before <b>5th August 2017</b> to qualify for the prize draw.
           <br>
           <br>
           Keep your phone on and charged and surveys will be sent automatically every few days.
           <br>
           <br>
           <b>It helps us if you click the button below whenever you are drinking alcohol, but don\'t worry if you forget.</b>
           </div> ]]>

    </string>
    <string name="full_responses">
        <![CDATA[
           <div style=\"font-size: 0.85em\">
           <b>Thanks! You\'ve completed 10 survey responses and have contributed valuable data to our research.</b>
           <br>
           <br>
           Unless you opted out, then your email address will be entered into the prize draw. Winners will be notified
           by 8th August 2017.
           <br>
           <br>
           The study will continue until 5th August 2017. If you keep AlcoSensing installed you\'ll help to
            contribute even more data to our research.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Thanks again for taking part in AlcoSensing.</b>
           </div> ]]>

    </string>
    <string name="study_end">
        <![CDATA[
           <div style=\"font-size: 0.85em\">
           <b>The study is now over and you should delete this app from your phone.</b>
           <br>
           <br>
           If you qualified for the prize draw, your email address will be entered. Winners will be notified
           by 8th August 2017.
           </div> ]]>

    </string>
    <string name="welcome_text" formatted="false">
        <![CDATA[
           <h2 style=\"text-align: center; font-family:sans-serif-light;\">Welcome to AlcoSensing</h2></div>
           <div style=\"font-size: 0.85em\">Thank you for downloading the AlcoSensing app. By downloading and
            using this app you’ll be helping with mobile sensing and machine
            learning research. Please read the following information carefully
            before you decide to take part.
            <br>
            <br>
            AlcoSensing is part of a research project conducted by a master’s
            student at Queen Mary University of London. If you continue to the
            following screens and register for this study you are agreeing to be
            a participant in this research project. You should only take part if
            you want to.
             <br>
             <br>
            If you don’t want to take part, you can uninstall this app by going to
            your phone settings now. No information will be recorded and you won’t
            be contacted.
             <br>
             <br>
            If you register and start using AlcoSensing but want to leave the study
            early, you are free to do so at any time. Just uninstall the app. Some
            data may have been recorded and will be used for research. If you’ve used
            the app for long enough you may still be entered into the prize draw, but
            you won’t be contacted for any other reason.
             <br>
             <br>
            If you decide you want to completely opt-out of the study and have all
            of your data deleted, you can email <a href=\"mailto:j.darby@se16.qmul.ac.uk?Subject=AlcoSensing%20Enquiry\">
            j.darby@se16.qmul.ac.uk</a> or <a href=\"mailto:laurissa.tokarchuk@qmul.ac.uk?Subject=AlcoSensing%20Enquiry\">
            laurissa.tokarchuk@qmul.ac.uk</a> and ask to be removed from the study without giving a reason.
             <br>
             <br>
            <b>For more information on what this study involves and what you need to
            do, click next.</b></div> ]]>

    </string>

    <string name="about_text">
        <![CDATA[
           <h2 style=\"text-align: center; font-family:sans-serif-light;\">What is this research about?</h2>
        "<div style=\"font-size: 0.85em\">
           In your hand right now you’re holding a very impressive piece of techology. Your phone
           contains lots of sensors used to measure  different things about the world around you.
           <br>
             <br>
           Some of these you probably already know about, like the GPS which tells your
           phone where you are. There’s also the accelerometer and gyroscope so that your phone
           can detect movement, but have you ever thought about the digital compass or the light and proximity sensors?
           <br>
             <br>
           All of these sensors produce data – numbers which represent things like how quickly you’re
           moving your phone, how bright or loud the room is, your location and so on.
           <br>
             <br>

           <b>AlcoSensing records some of this data from these sensors during certain time
           periods.</b> At the same time it records some information about your phone, like times
           when you switch your screen on or receive a notification.
           <br>
             <br>
           Don’t worry, we’re not interested in exactly what you do with your phone. <b>We’re only
           interested in data.</b> AlcoSensing won't record your calls
           or access your contacts. We won’t be able to read what’s in your messages and we
           won’t be able to look at your internet use, photos or the content of any other apps.
           <br>
             <br>

           After AlcoSensing records some data, we’ll send you a notification asking you
           to answer three quick questions about any alcohol you may have consumed
           recently (more about that later). The point of this research is to see if we can find
           a link between the data we collect from your phone, and how much you’ve had to drink.
           <br>
             <br>

           <b>If you’re happy to have data like this collected from your phone, please click next.</b>
           </div>"


        ]]>


    </string>

    <string name="how_text">
    <![CDATA[
           <h2 style=\"text-align: center; font-family:sans-serif-light;\">How does the app work?</h2></div>
           <div style=\"font-size: 0.85em\">
           AlcoSensing runs in the background. <b>You can continue to use your phone exactly as you
           always would.</b> Whenever AlcoSensing is recording some data you’ll see a notification.
           It uses up a bit more battery than usual, so we’ll try not to record data whenever your
           battery is low. If you don’t want any data recorded when you see the notification,
           just expand the notification and click to cancel; we won’t try again for 3 hours.
           <br>
             <br>
           When data recording ends the notification will disappear. Sometime later (perhaps the
           next morning) a different notification will pop up asking you to answer 3 questions
           related to a recent time period (e.g. 8pm to midnight last night). We’ll ask if you
           had anything to drink, how much you had to drink, and how drunk you felt. <b>Just answer
           the questions as accurately and truthfully as you can.</b>
           <br>
             <br>
           If you want to qualify for the prize draw <b>you need to allow the app to collect data and you need to respond
           to the survey notification at least 10 times.</b>
           <br>
             <br>
           We’ll only ask you the questions every 2-3 days. So you’ll have to keep the app installed
           on your phone for about a month to complete the study.
           <br>
             <br>
           We don’t want to use up your mobile data, so AlcoSensing data only gets uploaded to our
           server over WiFi. Please make sure you connect to a hotspot every now and then (the app
           status screen will tell you if it’s waiting for WiFi).
           <br>
             <br>
           If your phone switches off, the app will automatically restart in the background when
           you switch the phone back on. <b>Please don’t force close the app.</b> This will
           break things and you could lose your progress towards the prize draw.
           <br>
             <br>
           If we release an important app update to the Play Store, AlcoSensing will send you a notification.
           <b>Please make sure you keep the app up to date</b> or you may not receive surveys and won\'t
           be able to qualify for the prize draw.
           <br> <br>
           Only uninstall the app at the end of the study or if you decide you want to leave the study early.
           The AlcoSensing main screen will display a message when the study is over.
            <br><br>
           <b>If all of this sounds ok and you are happy to proceed, please click next.</b>
           </div> ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="requirements_text">
        <![CDATA[
           <div style=\"font-size: 0.9em\">
           In this research study we’re going to be asking you about drinking alcohol.
           <br>
           <br>
           It doesn’t matter how much you drink, you can still take part and enter the prize draw even if you never drink any alcohol at all.
           <br>
             <br>
           Because we’re talking about alcohol, we need to make sure that you meet certain requirements for this
           study.
           <br>
           <br>
           <b>Please tick the boxes next to the statements below <u>only if you agree</u>, then click next</b>:

           </div> ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="screening_fail_text">You haven\'t ticked all the boxes. You don\'t seem to meet the study requirements.\n
        \nThis study might not be right for you. To learn more about drinking alcohol, go to drinkaware.co.uk.\n
        \nNo data has been stored. You can now uninstall the app. Thanks for your interest in AlcoSensing.

    </string>

    <string name="consent_fail_text">You need to tick the box to give consent.\n
        \nPlease read the information carefully.\n
        \nIf you do not wish to take part, please uninstall the app.

    </string>

    <string name="consent_text" formatted="false">
    <![CDATA[
           <div style=\"font-size: 0.85em\">
           <b>At the bottom of this screen you are asked to provide your consent. Please only do this after
           you have read all of the information which explains this research on the previous screens. Please
           also read the notes here carefully.</b>
            <br>
           <br>
           You can click the back arrow above to re-read the previous screens.
            <br>
           <br>
           Title of study: “Can alcohol consumption and its acute effects be detected from smartphone sensor data?”
            <br>
           <br>
           Queen Mary Ethics of Research Committee Ref QMERC2017/26
            <br>
           <br>
           Thank you for considering taking part in this research. The person organizing the research has
           provided information which explains the project, which you should read before you agree to take part.
            <br>
           <br>
           If you have any questions arising from the information on previous screens, please ask the researcher
           before you decide whether to join in. You can contact the researcher by email at <a href=\"mailto:j.darby@se16.qmul.ac.uk?Subject=AlcoSensing%20Enquiry\">j.darby@se16.qmul.ac.uk</a> or the academic project supervisor at
            <a href=\"mailto:laurissa.tokarchuk@qmul.ac.uk?Subject=AlcoSensing%20Enquiry\">laurissa.tokarchuk@qmul.ac.uk</a>.
            <br>
           <br>
           You will be able to refer to this Consent Form inside the AlcoSensing app at anytime.
            <br>
           <br>
           <i>I understand that if I decide at any other time during the research that I no longer wish to participate
           in this project, I can notify the researchers involved and be withdrawn from it immediately.
            <br>
           <br>
           I consent to the processing of my personal information for the purposes of this research study. I
           understand that such information will be treated as strictly confidential and handled in accordance
           with the provisions of the Data Protection Act 1998.
            <br>
           <br>
           I agree that the research project named above has been explained to me to my satisfaction and I agree
           to take part in the study. I have read both the notes written above and the information screens about
           the project, and understand what the research study involves.</i>

           </div> ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="prize_text">
        <![CDATA[
        <div style=\"font-size: 0.85em\">
        At the end of the study two eligible participants will be chosen at random to each receive a £20 Amazon voucher.
        <br><br>
        To be an eligible participant, you must respond to 10 survey notifications.
        <br><br>
        Eligibility does not depend on the answers to the questions or how much alcohol you drink.
        <br><br>
        There is no requirement to drink any alcohol to be eligible for the prize draw.
        <br><br>
        Your app status screen will show how many surveys you have completed.
        <br><br>
        Only one entry per person.
        <br><br>
        If you are a winner, you agree to be contacted by email so that you can receive your voucher.
        </div> ]]>

    </string>

    <string name="data_protection_text">
        <![CDATA[
        <h2 style=\"text-align: center; font-family:sans-serif-light;\">Data Protection</h2></div>
        <div style=\"font-size: 0.85em\">
        The data we gather from you and your device during this study will be treated securely and confidentially.
        <br><br>
        Your data will not be used, transmitted or transferred to third parties for purposes other than for this study and other academic research.
        <br><br>
        We will use the Amazon Web Services S3 commercial cloud storage platform to store your data. This is
        a secure way to store your information, so you can be sure nobody other than the
        study researchers will be able to access your data.
        <br><br>
        Your data will be stored on servers located in the United Kingdom.
        <br><br>
        You can contact the researchers to request that your data is deleted at any time (see previous pages).
        <br><br>
        All of your data will be deleted when the study is complete.
        <br><br>
        </div>
        <h2 style=\"text-align: center; font-family:sans-serif-light;\">Study Concerns</h2></div>
        <div style=\"font-size: 0.85em\">
        If you have any questions or concerns about the manner in which the study was conducted please,
        in the first instance, contact the researcher responsible for the study. If this is unsuccessful,
        or not appropriate, please contact the Secretary at the Queen Mary Ethics of Research Committee,
        Room W104, Queen’s Building, Mile End Campus, Mile End Road, London or <a href=\"mailto:research-ethics@qmul.ac.uk?
        Subject=Study QMERC2017/26\">research-ethics@qmul.ac.uk</a>.
        </div> ]]>

    </string>

    <string name="drink_dialog_text">Thanks for completing the survey. You’re one step closer to qualifying for the prize draw!\n\n
        Just so you know, the UK Chief Medical Officer says it’s best not to drink more than 14 units
        of alcohol per week, and to spread it out over at least 3 days. It looks like you might drink
        more than this sometimes.\n\n
        Take a look at drinkware.co.uk if you want to learn more.\n\n
        Remember to keep your phone on and don’t force close the app. You’ll receive another survey soon.
        Click OK to go to your status screen.”
    </string>

    <string-array name="height_array">
        <item>metric</item>
        <item>feet/inches</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="weight_array">
        <item>metric</item>
        <item>st/lbs</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="me_credit">AlcoSensing was made by Joe Darby\n<a href= "www.github.com/joedarby">github.com/joedarby</a>
    </string>

    <string name="skit_credit">AlcoSensing uses SensingKit, a multi-platform sensing framework for large-scale experiments
        \n<a href= "sensingkit.org">sensingkit.org</a>
    </string>

    <string name="rstack_credit">AlcoSensing uses ResearchStack, an SDK and UX framework for building research study apps on Android
        \n<a href= "researchstack.org">researchstack.org</a>
    </string>

    <string name="icon_credit">AlcoSensing \"pint glass\"  icon made by <a href="www.freepik.com">Freepik</a>
        from <a href="www.flaticon.com">www.flaticon.com</a>

    </string>


</resources>
